<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Andrew Decker</title><link>https://zenpylon.me/</link><description>Recent content on Andrew Decker</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:05:23 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zenpylon.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Clang</title><link>https://zenpylon.me/posts/clang/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:05:23 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://zenpylon.me/posts/clang/</guid><description>Once upon a time, there was a conference about conferences. It was the conference con.
The con con. But secretly, it was all a deceptive scheme. A con.
The con con con. The attendants were all of them deceived. It was actually a conference on dancing the can-can.
The can-can con con con. At the end of the can-can, a man dressed as Genghis Khan came out of a cocoon to cheer the dancers.</description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://zenpylon.me/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2024 12:13:46 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://zenpylon.me/about/</guid><description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Andrew.
I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer based in Minneapolis. I really value curiosity, empathy, and self-reflection.
Outside of work, my hobbies include piano, meditation, running, and learning about basically anything. I&amp;rsquo;m a compulsive pun generator, and I feel a visceral delight in word play. Sorry in advance (I am not)!
I hold a B.A. in philosophy from the University of Minnesota.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://zenpylon.me/now/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zenpylon.me/now/</guid><description>Now or what I'm up to lately.
At a Glance 2024 I'm working to deepen my knowledge of computer science fundamentals via CS Primer and Napkin Math. I'm also taking a course at the University of Minnesota: EE5393 - Circuits, Computation, and Biology. Outside of that, I'm doing a lot of soul-searching.🌃 🔦
2023 I learned Scriabin's Op. 16, a set of 5 short, beautiful preludes. Here's my favorite recording. I worked for a company called NextEra Analytics, building internal tools to facilitate the economic assessment of prospective renewable energy projects.</description></item></channel></rss>