<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Andrew Decker</title><link>https://zenpylon.me/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Andrew Decker</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:05:23 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://zenpylon.me/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Clang</title><link>https://zenpylon.me/posts/clang/</link><pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2024 21:05:23 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://zenpylon.me/posts/clang/</guid><description>Once upon a time, there was a conference about conferences. It was the conference con.
The con con. But secretly, it was all a deceptive scheme. A con.
The con con con. The attendants were all of them deceived. It was actually a conference on dancing the can-can.
The can-can con con con. At the end of the can-can, a man dressed as Genghis Khan came out of a cocoon to cheer the dancers.</description><content type="html"><![CDATA[<div class="clang-fade">
  <p>
    Once upon a time, there was a conference about conferences. It was the
    conference con.<br />
    <em>The con con.</em>
  </p>

  <p>
    But secretly, it was all a deceptive scheme. A con.<br />
    <em>The con con con.</em>
  </p>

  <p>
    The attendants were all of them deceived. It was actually a conference on
    dancing the can-can.<br />
    <em>The can-can con con con.</em>
  </p>

  <p>
    At the end of the can-can, a man dressed as Genghis Khan came out of a
    cocoon to cheer the dancers.<br />
    <em>The can-can con con con Khan cocoon.</em>
  </p>

  <p>
    The cocoon had previously been used on the set of King Kong.<br />
    <em>The can-can con con con King Kong Khan cocoon.</em>
  </p>

  <p>
    But the event was also sponsored by Immanuel Kant society.<br />
    <em>The can-can Kant con con con King Kong Khan cocoon.</em>
  </p>

  <p>
    The man dressed as Genghis Khan held a moon-shaped balloon.<br />
    <em>The can-can Kant con con con King Kong Khan cocoon moon balloon.</em>
  </p>

  <p>
    On the balloon was a beautiful drawing of the Minnesota state bird, the
    loon.<br />
    <em
      >The can-can Kant con con con King Kong Khan cocoon loon moon balloon.</em
    >
  </p>

  <p>
    Genghis Khan sung a song in rejoicing:<br />
    <em
      >The can-can Kant con con con King Kong Khan cocoon loon moon balloon
      tune.</em
    >
  </p>

  <p><em>eeeeeeeeeee</em></p>
</div>
]]></content></item></channel></rss>